[{"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We had no choice but to stay but will take this as far as we can .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the participant \"We\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"He described Allawi 's face as that of a f*ed horse and he dismissed the whole government as a band of thieves and traitors .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"dismissed\", does the participant \"government\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Above all , we need a total absolute unity and determination of the civilized world against all three circles of evil .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"need\", does the participant \"unity\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"We were told that we could n't today because they were closing soon .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"closing\", does the participant \"they\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Debbie said , it is going to be hard on me to sale my old dodge truck .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"Debbie\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Bredders take the one that in not very interested and put it alone in a breeeding tank for 3 - 5 days .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"take\", does the participant \"Bredders\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"A state Senate committee is set today to start serving 16 subpoenas on electricity producers and officials who manage California 's energy grid to determine whether they acted in concert to manipulate energy prices .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"serving\", does the participant \"subpoenas\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"There is NO such thing as a BTA .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"is\", does the participant \"thing\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"My nails looked great for the better part of 2 weeks !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"looked\", does the participant \"nails\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"We came at around 730 and they close at 8 and wanted to try the specials but they were out for the day so I would say go way before they close .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"close\", does the participant \"they\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Iran in particular feared that Qanooni would loose and then be politically isolated from the mainstream .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"feared\", does the participant \"Iran\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"This BuzzMachine post argues that Google 's rush toward ubiquity might backfire -- which we 've all heard before , but it 's particularly well - put in this post .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"backfire\", does the participant \"rush\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They phoned the same day , confirmed it was the gearbox quoted me the job , I gave the go ahead .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"phoned\", does the participant \"They\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"He told us to stop by the salon and then he will tell us the price .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"told\", does the participant \"us\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I love it for discounted beauty items and household appliances .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"love\", does the participant \"it\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Disney cruises offer 24 - hour room services , and the crews are ready to serve you the way you like .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"offer\", does the participant \"cruises\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They had a room with a $ 99 rate , which I booked .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"booked\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I love this cage , it 's easy to clean , very spacious and fun for the hamster\"\nQuestion: In the event \"love\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Yahoo! Mail has the best spam protection around\"\nQuestion: In the event \"has\", does the participant \"Mail\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"It is our belief that this compensation plan will produce some of the largest checks in network marketing history .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"produce\", does the participant \"plan\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I figured it would end soon , but the money just kept coming in .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"figured\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Last June , an international initiative led by Japan to persuade the LTTE to come back to the negotiating table failed despite an aid package offer of US$ 4.5 billion .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"failed\", does the participant \"initiative\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"they use them to look prickly .. would you try to eat a cactus [ if u had no knife ] i know i would nt .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"use\", does the participant \"them\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I have to say the value of this place always amazes me .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"amazes\", does the participant \"me\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They said they were \" unable to tell me until they ordered my dress \" .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"ordered\", does the participant \"dress\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Louisiana 's Governor Blanco urged residents to spend Wednesday in prayer and assured them the crisis would eventually be overcome .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"urged\", does the participant \"Blanco\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"EVERYTHING IN HERE SEEMS TO AMAZE ME !!!\"\nQuestion: In the event \"SEEMS\", does the participant \"EVERYTHING\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I doubt he will be extradited to Venezuela , which is the only way that question could be answered with a Yes .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"extradited\", does the participant \"he\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I extend my hand to each of you in true friendship , and honor .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"extend\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Upon the same day he conquered Darius , won a great victory at sea , & died the same day .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"conquered\", does the participant \"Darius\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Lo and behold , they replaced the screen ( which had to be ordered ) yesterday and did n't charge me a dime .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"charge\", does the participant \"me\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"This place had the worst tasting pizza I have ever tasted it was possible the worst food I 've ever eaten .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"tasted\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"At the time , guardsmen were required to accumulate a minimum of 50 points to meet their yearly obligation .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"accumulate\", does the participant \"minimum\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The classes cover all age and skill ranges , with BALLROOM , LATIN , SEQUENCE , STREET , DISCO , LINE DANCING , BALLET , TAP & JAZZ .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"cover\", does the participant \"ranges\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They picked my car up in Yarmouth and towed to Bath for a great price .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"picked\", does the participant \"car\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Many online stores carry them , like Adorama :\"\nQuestion: In the event \"carry\", does the participant \"stores\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"His family loves him .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"loves\", does the participant \"family\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"We tried 4 different style of donuts , they were all the same when it came to quality .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"tried\", does the participant \"We\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"i have a baby eastern king snake .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"snake\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"They took on the challenge of making my Ferrari all I dreamed of and more .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"dreamed\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have to say that the baby does not scream after her of anything ... he / she sleeps .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"sleeps\", does the participant \"he\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"They were from all accounts marginalized and not listened to .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"marginalized\", does the participant \"They\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I ended up buying a birthday card and would probably come back for more .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"buying\", does the participant \"card\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I believe that these are three weekends in a row , January 6 , 13 and 20th .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"believe\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I know that we address audit rights in the LLC agreement so this may not matter anyway if this is a right they already have .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"address\", does the participant \"we\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Chahine said her immediate family spent about $ 20,000 to return to Detroit via Syria and Jordan .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"spent\", does the participant \"$\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"My vet told me when a dog is vomiting a lot , it could be a sign of obstruction .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"vomiting\", does the participant \"dog\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"She forwarded the Sommer letter to Stan and discussed it with him .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"forwarded\", does the participant \"letter\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Sanctuary serves delicious , somewhat healthy food in a great restaurant / fast food style .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"serves\", does the participant \"food\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Michele Tollis , Fabio 's father , began to attend metal concerts and festivals across Europe , handing out leaflets and quizzing Fabio 's friends .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"began\", does the participant \"Tollis\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The thing about The Script is they do not sound that Irish , I was surprised to hear they were from Dublin .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"is\", does the participant \"thing\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"As faith leaders , we commit ourselves to public action , visibility , education , and mutual support in the service of the right and freedom to marry .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"commit\", does the participant \"we\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" There have no business being there unless they are undermining Pakistan , '' says a Pakistani official .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"undermining\", does the participant \"Pakistan\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"He responded \" we have problem with ' people ' \" .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"responded\", does the participant \"He\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Well , they have a variety of sports that they play like basketball , soccer , etc .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"play\", does the participant \"they\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I called and got the same runaround on hold and noone calls you back .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"called\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"i want to hook up with that girl paige in the brown leather jacket .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"want\", does the participant \"i\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Her husband became a citizen of the US just the week before last .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"became\", does the participant \"husband\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"As a result there was a problem with the weapon jamming .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"was\", does the participant \"problem\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"\" You say , ' wow ! '\"\nQuestion: In the event \"say\", does the participant \"You\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I assume his actual reason is that he 's worried that Berkshire Hathaway just ca n't grow quickly enough to justify his usual charity policy .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"assume\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I want to use this opportunity to welcome Brian Ryner to Google !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"welcome\", does the participant \"Ryner\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The initial reservoir reports estimate reserves of 80 - 120 million barrels of sour crude and they estimate initial production to be 40,000 bpd starting in 1Q 2003 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"estimate\", does the participant \"reports\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I enjoyed the animations and wanted to share them with my friends .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"share\", does the participant \"them\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"( News assistant Bobby Bender recalls the letter containing the items to have been addressed to The Sun . )\"\nQuestion: In the event \"recalls\", does the participant \"letter\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Bradley 's record of 300 phenophases found that even prior to 1999 , spring was arriving in higher latitudes several weeks earlier than in the earlier years of her data .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"arriving\", does the participant \"spring\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The biggest LTTE maritime disaster was reported in the now - defunct Asiaweek in 2001 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"reported\", does the participant \"disaster\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"As faith leaders , we commit ourselves to public action , visibility , education , and mutual support in the service of the right and freedom to marry .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"commit\", does the participant \"ourselves\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Yet people seem willing -- even eager -- to accommodate mountain lions , despite the risks .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"accommodate\", does the participant \"lions\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I know that with my industry - wide and investment banking contacts that I can help raise capital for the fund .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"know\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"There is a painting on my wall in the Oval -- first of all , I do n't know .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"is\", does the participant \"painting\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"They told me that this is not under warranty and want to charge me $ 175 just to diagnose the problem !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"told\", does the participant \"They\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"you need to bring me next time\"\nQuestion: In the event \"bring\", does the participant \"me\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"On my panel , Loretta Lynch asked Reliant and Duke to supply her with the details of the contracts they cut to sell their power forward to marketers .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"supply\", does the participant \"her\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I guess they figured me for an easy mark , and tried to explain that my car would n't pass unless I replaced a hose .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"figured\", does the participant \"me\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"My last rabbit did that a few times , and he was fine ...\"\nQuestion: In the event \"did\", does the participant \"rabbit\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They fixed the queso !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fixed\", does the participant \"They\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"They wish to launch on Sept. 1 - meaning we will need to be sending mailings sometime around mid-August .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"wish\", does the participant \"They\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" I do n't know how these events could have taken place without some concerted effort , \" said Dunn .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"Dunn\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"You need to check out the French Indochina War ( 1946 - 1954 ) not the Vietnam War ( 1957 - 1975 ) .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"check\", does the participant \"War\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"You said you liked her and she accepted it as a truth and perhaps as a compliment , but it does not mean she fancies you or wants to pair off with you .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"accepted\", does the participant \"she\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I enjoyed working with all of you during the past five years at Enron / Azurix , and I wish you all of the best .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"wish\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Fried rice has NO flavor , it literally taste like water .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"has\", does the participant \"rice\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Musk , which is scraped from their genitals once a day for as long as they can surv ive , makes the scent of perfume last a bit longer after each application .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"makes\", does the participant \"Musk\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I visited their huge Chicago lighting showroom and all I have to say is WOW !!\"\nQuestion: In the event \"visited\", does the participant \"showroom\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Dr. Wallen explained the procedure in detail and took his time with me .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"explained\", does the participant \"Wallen\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I called the store and the clerk giggled , and agreed that it was gross , but said it was not her problem .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"giggled\", does the participant \"clerk\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The situation appears to be even worse in Mississippi .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"appears\", does the participant \"situation\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"'' President Musharraf promised to help us and cooperate with us on curbing terrorist activity by the Taliban , '' says Karzai .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"curbing\", does the participant \"activity\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I ran into Corey last night at LW s and I am thinking this is a girl for Darren .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"ran\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Records show that on Oct. 31 , power generators and electricity traders filed letters with the Federal Energy Regulatory Commission , demanding that the new plan be killed .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"filed\", does the participant \"generators\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I called over the weekend due to clogged kitchen sink .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"called\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I use propane with a blower and a burner I built http://www.mikegigi.com/meltmetl.htm and http://www.mikegigi.com/firehole.htm\"\nQuestion: In the event \"built\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"\" There is always the possibility they could jam us up , make us look like we are not numero uno , \" Pike said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"jam\", does the participant \"us\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The other stylists around me kept pressuring me saying he 's so wonderful , you 're going to love your hair .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"pressuring\", does the participant \"me\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"they all need love and attn , food , proper surroundings etc .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"need\", does the participant \"they\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We love our new roof !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"love\", does the participant \"We\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Peter Dale Scott includes an account of how Terrell 's whistleblowing was stifled by them in his book Cocaine Politics .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"stifled\", does the participant \"whistleblowing\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"You informed me that you would discuss this with your attorney .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"discuss\", does the participant \"you\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Dessert was ... hmmm , that 's interesting , I do n't even remember dessert .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"remember\", does the participant \"dessert\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" There have no business being there unless they are undermining Pakistan , '' says a Pakistani official .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"says\", does the participant \"official\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I want to party hardy for my birthday :)\"\nQuestion: In the event \"want\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They worked for me and I hope they worked for you !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"hope\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The money funds their travel , explosives , hideouts and permanent search for soft vulnerable targets .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"funds\", does the participant \"money\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I found them and purchased both from a gallery in London , William Weston .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"purchased\", does the participant \"both\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I have no doubt that the rescue is wonderful .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Cover letters and resumes need to be perfect .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"need\", does the participant \"letters\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"My wife has a slight impediment in her speech .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"has\", does the participant \"impediment\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"India 's Andaman and Nicobar Islands comprise more than 500 islands lying 1,000 kilometers east of Sri Lanka in the Bay of Bengal .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"comprise\", does the participant \"Islands\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"\" They can freely write anything they like about our prophet , but if one raises doubts about the Holocaust he is either fined or sent to prison , \" he added .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"write\", does the participant \"anything\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We played a new version of Uno called \" African Uno \" that was complex , fast and at times , physically challenging .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"played\", does the participant \"We\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I have no complaints about the service I received .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"complaints\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I trust you and believe that you 'll be able to handle this and all you have to do is to reciprocate !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"trust\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I think that this is for you since I do n't know any of these people .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"think\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The dramatic increase in radiation - induced thyroid cancers in children and adolescents in Belarus , Russia , and Ukraine , which have been observed since 1991 , continues to this day .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"continues\", does the participant \"increase\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The last I checked , the Satanists have a long way to go to catch up with the death and destruction dealt out by self - proclaimed ( though false ) Christians .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"checked\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"there 's these little like bait worms at jack s . petshoppe .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"'s\", does the participant \"worms\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"In Baghdad Kadhim Talal Husain , assistant dean at the School of Education at Mustansiriyah University , was assassinated with his driver in the Salikh district .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"assassinated\", does the participant \"Husain\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I thought I would have to wait until I went home to NYC .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"thought\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Enron continues to feel free to move me around at will .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"continues\", does the participant \"Enron\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" All you have to do is look at the photographs , \" Ed Bangs , wolf recovery coordinator for the U.S. Fish and Wildlife Service , told UPI 's Blue Planet ,\"\nQuestion: In the event \"told\", does the participant \"Bangs\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"By comparison , outdoor cats have a life expectancy of 3 - 7 years depending on how many predators are in the local environment .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"cats\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"In an apparently unrelated incidents , some eleven Iraqis were killed by snipers on Tuesday , including a group of police trainees in a bus near Hilla and two police in Kirkuk .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"killed\", does the participant \"Iraqis\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I have a concern that the Enron optionality bug could bite us on the backside with that one .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"concern\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The poor quality starts at the receptionist desk , where the staff is very impatient and lack the efficiency I once loved about the office .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"lack\", does the participant \"efficiency\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I found an injured pure white bird ( dove I guess ? )\"\nQuestion: In the event \"guess\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The referenced TAGG # was entered as a ' New Counterparty ' , can you please let me know what counterparty this is so we can correctly assess the counterparty exposure .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"assess\", does the participant \"exposure\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I promise you that if you follow the directions exactly that you will start making more money than you thought possible by doing something so easy !!\"\nQuestion: In the event \"follow\", does the participant \"directions\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The dealer wanted $ 1300 to fix that and another $ 1500 to fix some other things .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"wanted\", does the participant \"$\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"A lack of organisation , coupled with the distain for its customers , makes this the worst rental agency I have used .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"makes\", does the participant \"this\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I propose we have a conference call with Bob Fagan on Fri July 20 at 1:00 pm Calgary time to discuss any areas of concern / confusion you may have .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"propose\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I was amazed at the spiel they delivered .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"delivered\", does the participant \"they\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I want signed and numbered .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"want\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Guerrillas threatened to assassinate Prime Minister Iyad Allawi and Minister of Defense Hazem Shaalan in retaliation for the attack .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"threatened\", does the participant \"Guerrillas\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I bought about half of the furniture I own from this place .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"bought\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Yeah you got ta burn it .. that s the only way\"\nQuestion: In the event \"got\", does the participant \"you\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Prices for electricity jumped from an average of $ 249 a megawatt to $ 700 a megawatt within three days , ISO records show .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"jumped\", does the participant \"Prices\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I ordered a kid meal with a milk and found a bottle was half opened already .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"ordered\", does the participant \"meal\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Some conservationists want the protection extended so wolves can move into other states , including Colorado , Utah and Oregon , among others .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"want\", does the participant \"protection\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I believe the message you forwarded to me belongs to the Mark Taylor at EI ( based in London ) .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"forwarded\", does the participant \"you\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"rumor has feb 05 on the calender .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"has\", does the participant \"rumor\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The painting is based upon the hymn called , ' A Charge to Keep . '\"\nQuestion: In the event \"based\", does the participant \"painting\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I suggest a \" blind draw \" on the teams , best ball not scramble on the golf , and as for the wager , no emails from the losing team for one week !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"suggest\", does the participant \"draw\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"That 's overstating it , I know .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"know\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The Pakistani press reported that she was nabbed in Karachi after being spotted at the airport in late March or early April 2003 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"nabbed\", does the participant \"she\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I have 3 children there and they are the Best .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"children\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Shanna , I spoke with Per tonight about this .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"spoke\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"She gave me amazing pictures at an amazing price and made my wedding day so memorable .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"gave\", does the participant \"She\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I detect the hissing lisp of the lying serpent in this article .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"detect\", does the participant \"lisp\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I have a new born daughter and she helped me with a lot .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"daughter\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They offer a good portions at a great price , it 's enough food to fill you up , but you do n't ever feel like you ate too much .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"offer\", does the participant \"They\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Only Irish coffee provides in a single glass all four essential food groups : alcohol , caffeine , sugar and fat .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"provides\", does the participant \"coffee\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"JUNO AND OPEN I LOVE YOU GUYS !!!!!!!!!!!!!!\"\nQuestion: In the event \"LOVE\", does the participant \"YOU\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I have the opportunity to pick up a super nice 6 year old for free .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"** Google defies US over search data **\"\nQuestion: In the event \"defies\", does the participant \"US\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"His one - day mission vaulted his communist homeland into the elite circle of spacefaring nations - Russia and the United States - that can launch and sustain humans in space .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"launch\", does the participant \"humans\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I knew a cat that died in its sleep aged 21 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"knew\", does the participant \"cat\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"But the menu had standard stuff that one would get at a Belgian Tavern .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the participant \"menu\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The missile 's manufacturers state that one or two missiles could cripple a destroyer , and five missiles could sink a 20,000 ton ship .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"cripple\", does the participant \"destroyer\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The next day , the federal commission killed the new pricing plan .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"killed\", does the participant \"plan\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Yesterday evening , the Posada story was featured in the public television news show in Germany ( ARD , Tagesthemen ) .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"featured\", does the participant \"ARD\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I did an overnight in a home stay that was sweet and the water market was wonderful .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"did\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have a new born daughter and she helped me with a lot .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"He refused to believe them and ordered the military to win the war within two to three years ( before the next election in 1968 ) .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"believe\", does the participant \"them\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Al Qaeda had a motive in mind .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the participant \"Qaeda\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Senator Patrick Leahy at a Congressional hearing in the Spring of 2002 noted that the FBI had collected the Ames strain from 20 sources .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"noted\", does the participant \"Leahy\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"A state Senate committee is set today to start serving 16 subpoenas on electricity producers and officials who manage California 's energy grid to determine whether they acted in concert to manipulate energy prices .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"acted\", does the participant \"they\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Your buddy Beau invited me .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"invited\", does the participant \"buddy\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I like I Move CA - Los Angeles Movers , they moved me before , but this time they were awesome :)\"\nQuestion: In the event \"like\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"My last rabbit did that a few times , and he was fine ...\"\nQuestion: In the event \"did\", does the participant \"that\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Family owned and operated makes sure the atmosphere is relaxed and the food home - cooked with style .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"cooked\", does the participant \"food\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"My cat had a seizure yesterday and was ill .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the participant \"cat\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I was told to leave a restaurant because I ordered water with my meal ( apparently this is \" washing down \" your food \" ) and not ordering wine .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"told\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Jana made me feel very comfortable .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"made\", does the participant \"Jana\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Iranian officials say they made no objections to Khan 's ouster because they want to strengthen Karzai 's campaign against warlords .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"say\", does the participant \"officials\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"They provide an emotional infrastructure for atrocities .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"provide\", does the participant \"infrastructure\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They love leaf or romaine lettuce and tomatos , celery , cucumbers , carrots .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"love\", does the participant \"lettuce\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"US - trained Malaysian biochemist Yazid Sufaat met with 9/11 plotters and two hijackers in January 2000 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"met\", does the participant \"Sufaat\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We felt that the menu had a little more variety on the Mariner of the Seas .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"felt\", does the participant \"We\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I enjoyed my tour and i am looking for adventure tour and India heritage tours for valuable .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"enjoyed\", does the participant \"tour\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I get that careless teenager kind of treatment from some of their staff ... perhaps they should hire more serious adults to help serve / cook .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"hire\", does the participant \"adults\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I know that we address audit rights in the LLC agreement so this may not matter anyway if this is a right they already have .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"know\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They refused .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"refused\", does the participant \"They\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"It is rumored that North Korea has at least a couple nuclear weapons .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"rumored\", does the participant \"It\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I mean , that 's the way it works at amusement parks : the longest lines are at the best rides .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"mean\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Today 's incident proves that Sharon has lost his patience and his hope in peace .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"lost\", does the participant \"patience\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We made the decision for a couple of reasons .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"made\", does the participant \"We\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I did the work myself for $ 50 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"did\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Several candidates were assassinated and targeted these last two weeks , others have been forced under threats to withdraw and to follow the example of the Islamic party .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"forced\", does the participant \"others\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Chahine said her immediate family spent about $ 20,000 to return to Detroit via Syria and Jordan .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"spent\", does the participant \"family\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The letter bombs were sent in connection with the treatment of the Egyptian islamists imprisoned for the earlier attack on the WTC and a related plot .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"sent\", does the participant \"bombs\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The S100 has a slightly larger screen and the new digic 5 processor .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"has\", does the participant \"screen\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I think they may even be better than the pair I have been using this past year !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"think\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The office refused my requests to see what they got from BC / BS .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"refused\", does the participant \"office\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The 99 - tonne cache of AK47s was to have been secretly flown out from a US base in Bosnia .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"was\", does the participant \"cache\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"At the time , guardsmen were required to accumulate a minimum of 50 points to meet their yearly obligation .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"meet\", does the participant \"obligation\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We live within 20 miles of the hotel and wanted to get away from our responsibilities for the night .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"live\", does the participant \"We\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"U.S. President George W. Bush shakes hands with Chinese President Hu Jintao in a bilateral meeting in Santiago .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"shakes\", does the participant \"Bush\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I know I need some of your organizational skills .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"know\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"We are resolved that the State should not interfere with same - gender couples who choose to marry and share fully and equally in the rights , responsibilities , and commitments of civil marriage .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"choose\", does the participant \"couples\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I got a coupon from Pennysaver for this station .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"got\", does the participant \"coupon\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"They did that with no problem .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"did\", does the participant \"They\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Zawahiri said that the US should expect another 9/11 on US soil .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"Zawahiri\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Security in the hotel seemed to be excellent , but we were never given an explanation as to why someone would open these items .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"open\", does the participant \"someone\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The Americans detected the attempt to infiltrate the urban areas and were already redeploying troops from the rural areas .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"detected\", does the participant \"attempt\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I urge all St. Thomas the Apostle parishioners and all of South Florida residents to come see Gus !!!\"\nQuestion: In the event \"urge\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They both went to jail and a new manager was put in charge of the apartments .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"went\", does the participant \"They\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"We had to throw out about 80 percent of our meals because the food tasted so horrible .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"throw\", does the participant \"percent\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Once upon a time ( in 2001 , to be specific ) , the Coca - Cola corporation built a bottling plant in a small and remote Indian village in the state of Kerala .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"built\", does the participant \"corporation\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I apologize , I 'm on the road and have n't heard when that will be .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"apologize\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" Success comes before work \" only in the dictionary\"\nQuestion: In the event \"comes\", does the participant \"Success\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Jim Lobe has more on the political implications of the Fallujah assault , both in Iraq and in Washington .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"has\", does the participant \"Lobe\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have a few how to videos for DIY 35 mm film in a 120 camera on my YouTube channel :\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"A team from the court managed to take his deposition before he died .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"died\", does the participant \"he\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"they recovered the pics geeksquad deleted .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"recovered\", does the participant \"pics\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"They came to my house in no time and started working on the gate .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"came\", does the participant \"They\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I saw this place and it looked like the HOLY GRAIL .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"saw\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I knew a cat that died in its sleep aged 21 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"died\", does the participant \"cat\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I MAKE MONEY NOT DEAL WITH BROKERS \" Wow , can you believe in today s tough times this dealership would be looking for any way to move vehicles .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"MAKE\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Michael helped shoot the majority of my firm 's website and we could not have been happier .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"helped\", does the participant \"Michael\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I had my horse transported from CA to WA and he came on this big , open stock trailer .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"transported\", does the participant \"horse\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"This type of harness goes around the dog s chest and legs and has a clip for the leash up on the back of the dog in middle of shoulder blades .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"goes\", does the participant \"type\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Miramar was founded September 20 1888 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"founded\", does the participant \"Miramar\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"A little birdie told me that you were checking into tickets for Seoul .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"checking\", does the participant \"you\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"More people die from AIDS in one day in Africa than all the Russians who died in the hands of Chechnya - based Moslem suicide murderers since that conflict started .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"die\", does the participant \"people\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"He gave no indication on the value of the highest bid .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"gave\", does the participant \"He\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They said it was \" plugs and wires \" and quoted me $ 330 to do the work , including parts .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"quoted\", does the participant \"me\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I had no problem with my delivery .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the participant \"problem\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The only neurological sign that he shows is that he barely drags his toes and sometimes has trouble with his right lead .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"is\", does the participant \"sign\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I have a Norwegian Forest Cat that is named Achilles bc as a kitten he always attacked your feet when you walked by !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"attacked\", does the participant \"he\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I expected to pay for this service , but imagine my surprise when I received a bill for MORE than what I paid to have the original return prepared .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"paid\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"But they remain uncertain about whether China aims to beat the United States to the moon in its secretive space effort .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"remain\", does the participant \"they\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"China wanted an overland route through its own territory , which would give it ultimate control if hostilities broke out .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"wanted\", does the participant \"route\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"You have two adjustment screws for up and down and right to left positions .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"screws\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Robinson said the emergency order allowed the ISO to secure refunds should overcharges for electricity be proven to federal officials .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"Robinson\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"A little birdie told me that you were checking into tickets for Seoul .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"told\", does the participant \"me\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The storm threatened oil installations in the Gulf of Mexico where about one - quarter of US oil operations are based .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"threatened\", does the participant \"installations\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Cities such as Falluja received special treatment from Saddam and enjoyed a disproportionate share of the country 's wealth and power .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"received\", does the participant \"treatment\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Abdel Rahman 's son was captured in Quetta , Pakistan in mid-February 2003 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"captured\", does the participant \"son\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I sent a graphic that would have been distorted if printed as it was .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"sent\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"My assistant Joanne Rozycki has cell , car numbers to reach me .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"has\", does the participant \"assistant\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I suspect the streets of Baghdad will look as if a war is looming this week .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"suspect\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They needed someone that could convince the jury they had been able to see all relevant documents in CIA files on Wilson .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"convince\", does the participant \"someone\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I love them !!!\"\nQuestion: In the event \"love\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I saw a site that charges $ 0.70 per mile .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"saw\", does the participant \"site\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I took the original piece of metal and rigged it to make due since I had to complete the job .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"complete\", does the participant \"job\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I frequent this resturant on a weekly basis but usally only for lunch .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"frequent\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"\" Iran has significant capabilities for asymmetric warfare , and poses the additional threat of proliferation .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"has\", does the participant \"Iran\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"But the articles I read seemed to say the contrary .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"read\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"( I think there are close to 24,000 groups )\"\nQuestion: In the event \"think\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I found this on a bulletin board and decided to try it : I do n't care about the useless pre-fabricated crap this message usually says .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"found\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I thought that I had gained my cockatiel 's trust , but now he 's not coming to me when I open his cage .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"thought\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"i have stronger will than you think .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"will\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"\" At some point , Patricia tripped or the bear tripped her and was at her back .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"tripped\", does the participant \"her\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"But if -- there 's a painting on the wall in the Oval Office that shows a horseman charging up a steep cliff , and there are at least two other horsemen following .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"shows\", does the participant \"horseman\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"We love our new roof !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"love\", does the participant \"roof\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"At one point they told me the dog had been fixed , the next day it had n't .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fixed\", does the participant \"dog\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I see that we are scheduled to have lunch today .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"scheduled\", does the participant \"we\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"At 3:15 am on night # 2 , the fire alarm and strobe light activated in my room .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"activated\", does the participant \"alarm\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"ALITO filed a dissenting opinion , in which SCALIA and THOMAS joined as to Parts I through III .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"filed\", does the participant \"ALITO\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Al Qaeda members and sympathizers feel that the FBI 's involvement in countries like Egypt , Saudi Arabia , Pakistan , Indonesia , and the Philippines interferes with the sovereignty of those countries .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"feel\", does the participant \"members\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I started collecting animations & jokes just to help with my boredom and depression .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"started\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"He has encyclopedic knowledge of hundreds of different Supreme Court cases , and he can recite details from memory .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"has\", does the participant \"He\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Secretive efforts keep outsiders in the dark about the program 's goals\"\nQuestion: In the event \"keep\", does the participant \"outsiders\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"There are special regions uniquely and imposingly designed for the children .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"are\", does the participant \"regions\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I came to find out the person was the hotel OWNER also .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"came\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They interviewed me , gave me tests in the software I included on my resume , and placed me in a position that I kept for several years .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"included\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"We love everything about the fence .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"love\", does the participant \"We\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Sussexs have soft feathers .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"feathers\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"They kept the name Oracle and created the RDBMS engine .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"created\", does the participant \"engine\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I got this .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"got\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The bear dwarfed the 6 - foot - 1 Mr. Parenteau , knocking him to the ground , he said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"dwarfed\", does the participant \"Parenteau\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Xinhua reports that a wide range of Iraqi political forces on Tuesday condemned Sharon 's murder of Sheikh Ahmed Yassin , a religious leader of Hamas , the day before .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"condemned\", does the participant \"murder\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"But today , I got a boy and realized that he is HUGE !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"got\", does the participant \"boy\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The only reason I switched away from them in the first place is because my good friend who apprenticed with them was starting out on his own .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"apprenticed\", does the participant \"friend\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Within seven days , I started getting money in the mail !!\"\nQuestion: In the event \"started\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I said great and Dan arrived on time at 10 am to make the repair .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"He needs more info about these trades ( i.e. , price info ) and would like to talk with you about it .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"needs\", does the participant \"info\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" There 's no tracking mechanism in place \" ?!?!?\"\nQuestion: In the event \"'s\", does the participant \"mechanism\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"First room had used tissues next to the bed and I requested it be rectified .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"requested\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I was married by a judge .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"married\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"My car broke down and roadside towed my vehicle to Sussman Kia .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"broke\", does the participant \"car\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I know it s in the wrong catagory , but still , I wrote this question for a reason , not for you to critisize me .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"critisize\", does the participant \"me\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"They came on time and completed their work quickly .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"came\", does the participant \"They\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Derrick did a terrible job , was a complete jerk the entire time , and I had no warning as to the price .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"did\", does the participant \"Derrick\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"A NATO spokesman said : \" There 's no tracking mechanism to ensure they do n't fall into the wrong hands .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fall\", does the participant \"they\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"i want a small indoor pet that my mother will let me have please help\"\nQuestion: In the event \"let\", does the participant \"me\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"For weeks , reporters scoured Alabama in search of pilots or anyone who might have remembered seeing Mr. Bush at the time he was serving in the National Guard there .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"scoured\", does the participant \"Alabama\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Is there any other way to communicate or do your friends only understand text .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"understand\", does the participant \"friends\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"'' Pakistan now has a large force deployed in Baluchistan which was not there before , '' says Lt. General David Barno .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"says\", does the participant \"Barno\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have wavy hair and she cut to my hair style .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"cut\", does the participant \"she\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I have lots of containers in there .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They have the best prices locally and good customer service .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"prices\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Dignitaries condemn the act but visit her bereaved family and the money flows .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"condemn\", does the participant \"act\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I enjoyed my tour and i am looking for adventure tour and India heritage tours for valuable .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"enjoyed\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"It has two parts , both of which are timed for 90 seconds each and the differential between the resulting two scores determines the likelihood of having a learning disability or attention deficit disorder .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"timed\", does the participant \"both\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Al - Sharq al - Awsat reports that a key eyewitness in the trial of Saddam Hussein for a 1982 massacre at Dujail has died .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"died\", does the participant \"eyewitness\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Just today I bought a medium rat for my beloved Ball Python Salazar ( name after Harry Potter ) .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"bought\", does the participant \"rat\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They gave the best service & rates I could find .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"gave\", does the participant \"They\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The mysterious RAPHAEL Holinshed was named for the mysterious Neoplatonic Italian painter RAPHAEL Sanzio who painted _ St. George Fighting the Dragon _ ( 1504 - 06 )\"\nQuestion: In the event \"named\", does the participant \"Holinshed\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"She has to iron her pants on the driveway .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"has\", does the participant \"She\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Cj and company did all that we ask and 10 times more .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"did\", does the participant \"Cj\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We pointed out to the PX that there was excess credit .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"pointed\", does the participant \"We\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I went to this urgent care center and was blown away with their service .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"went\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Either I suck at my own style or Janice is a genius .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"suck\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"TEXAS ROADHOUSE HAS VERY GOOD MEALS , THAT THE MEAT COMES RIGHT OFF THE BONES .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"HAS\", does the participant \"MEALS\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I found my initial selection satisfactory but the wine flight we chose to be poorly composed .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"chose\", does the participant \"we\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I called and asked about the price for hair updo and the receptionist or owner who aswered the phone refused to tell me , or even just give me an approximate price range .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"called\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have a Saab ... which everything is expensive on and they have been extrememly fair and price a lot lower than any other shop I called .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"Saab\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I have a preorder and am even considering getting a second preorder to have multiple accounts .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"These animals have the misfortune to produce a substance that is useful in the manufacture of perfume .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"animals\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The bill reduces ISS operations by $ 120 million due to the continued reduced capability of the ISS for at least half of FY05 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"reduces\", does the participant \"operations\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Sufaat was arrested in December 2001 upon his return to Malaysia .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"arrested\", does the participant \"Sufaat\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"You have two adjustment screws for up and down and right to left positions .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"You\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I shoot a t1i and have n't had such an issue .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"shoot\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"\" Their screams changed , \" Dr. Fortier said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"Fortier\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I knew what it was and told the guy that it was n't a fps .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"knew\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"China launches its second manned spaceflight mission\"\nQuestion: In the event \"launches\", does the participant \"China\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"In the Oct. 31 letters , electricity producers told federal officials that if price caps were n't removed it would lead to a collapse of the energy market .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"told\", does the participant \"producers\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I use propane with a blower and a burner I built http://www.mikegigi.com/meltmetl.htm and http://www.mikegigi.com/firehole.htm\"\nQuestion: In the event \"use\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Hi , I want to get a few pet rats and need a rat cage .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"want\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"My father re-secured the petroleum assets of Kuwait in 1991 at a cost of sixty - one billion U.S. dollars ( $ 61,000,000,000 ) .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"re-secured\", does the participant \"father\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I needed a part for my appliance , the cost was very high so I said never mind , paid the fee and called a local business for a second quote .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"paid\", does the participant \"fee\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"On my panel , Loretta Lynch asked Reliant and Duke to supply her with the details of the contracts they cut to sell their power forward to marketers .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"asked\", does the participant \"Lynch\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"i have a 1 and a half year old male neutered cat and a new 2 month old spayed female kitten .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"cat\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I ordered a kid meal with a milk and found a bottle was half opened already .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"ordered\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We order take out from here all the time and we are never disappointed .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"order\", does the participant \"We\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Justin , I have no knowledge of any bad faith actins Enron has pending in Texas but I will call Richard Sanders who manages domestic litgation here .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"manages\", does the participant \"Sanders\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Newer semi-automatic wangs have a rail built into the receiver under the shaft .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"wangs\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I used my card to purchase a meal on the menu and the total on my receipt was $ 8.95 but when I went on line to check my transaction it show $ 10.74 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"used\", does the participant \"card\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"He told me \" no problem , we will match the offer or do better . \"\"\nQuestion: In the event \"match\", does the participant \"we\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I think this place is probably really great especially judging by the reviews on here .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"think\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"All I can say is that Elmira you are the best I ve experienced , never before has the seamstress done a perfect job until i met you .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"met\", does the participant \"you\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"\" My first thought was to push it away , \" he said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"push\", does the participant \"it\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"A girl raises her hand .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"raises\", does the participant \"hand\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The name was derived from the founder 's name Dr. Michael Cowpland .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"derived\", does the participant \"name\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}]